healthyandnaturalworld.com 2018-01-08

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how healthyandnaturalworld.com uses and protects any information that you provide when you use this website.

healthyandnaturalworld.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

healthyandnaturalworld.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from November 28, 2012.

This site may collect identifiable information such as names and email addresses when voluntarily submitted or used when posting a comment. We do not share/spam/sale this information to anyone; except in cases required by law or to prevent fraud or to prevent damage to anyone in whatever form. When visiting this site a cookie maybe placed on your hard drive to provide you better access to the site, but in no way it give us access to your computer or to any personally identifiable information stored on your computer.

Third-party advertisers like Google, may also place and read cookies on your browser to serve ads on this site or use tracking technology to collect information. You can choose not to accept these cookies. Google also uses DART cookie that enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

Information collected by third parties may be combined with information collected across different websites, online services, and other linked or associated devices. These third parties may use your information to improve their own services and consistent with their own privacy policies.

You may opt out by visiting:

  * <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices>

This website has links, when you click links to other websites to leave our site, we do not anymore have control over that website. Please note that this site does not accept responsibility for the activities of any third party listing on this site, including ads or the content they provide. By using this site you are agreeing to this condition.

The entire content of this website is copyrighted and should never be reproduced/copied to another website without written authorization from the owner.
